<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on YINING XU</title>
    <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on YINING XU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Yining Xu.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yining-xu.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Ninja</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/foodninja/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/foodninja/</guid>
      <description>This is a cooking App design inspired my mom who can always make wonders by using food ingredients left in the refrigerator .
 Introduction This App called “FoodNinja” which offers recipes for a healthy and quick meal which can be easily processed by novices. It is also dedicated to dealing with the food ingredients left in the refrigerator in an effective way which don’t need to be worried about, just like what a Ninja can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dilemma of Euthanasia</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/euthanasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/euthanasia/</guid>
      <description>A data journalism work in the course &amp;lsquo;Data Mining and Visualisation&amp;rsquo;, 2019
 The Dilemma of Euthanasia: A Decent End or The Hope for Living? On June 7th of 2018, the well-known Taiwanese sports anchor Mr.Fu Daren bid farewell to the pain and the world after a two-hour assisted suicide at the Dignity Clinic in Switzerland, which triggers public discussion in China because not everyone has the opportunity to make such a choice——euthanasisa is yet illegal in China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is the next new social media platform?</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/blockchain/</guid>
      <description>I came up with this decentralised social network when discussing the current application of blockchain in China with my fellows in the Infinite Studio.
 The best feature of my proposed project is the equal relationship between the platform and users. Firstly, users will be able to decide the extent to which they can safely exchange their data for profits. The blockchain technology will also enable users to easily transfer their social media accounts to a safer platform without worrying about the potentially huge opportunity cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zootopia</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/zootopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/zootopia/</guid>
      <description>A magazine design inspired by my travelling in Vietnam. *Designed it in the eternal summer of Vietnam.*`
This is my first Adobe Indesign practice: a magazine design which is inspired by my trip in the zoo at Vietnam during reading week of 2018 autumn.
Design Concept Shadow play is one of the oldest Chinese dramas, which is beloved by children. I used the silhouttes for reference to design the cover of this magazine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>