<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on YINING XU</title>
    <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on YINING XU</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2020, Yining Xu.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yining-xu.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dignity of Death</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/hugoisforlovers%E7%9A%84%E5%89%AF%E6%9C%AC/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/hugoisforlovers%E7%9A%84%E5%89%AF%E6%9C%AC/</guid>
      <description> A data journalism work done in the course &amp;lsquo;Data Mining and Visualisation&amp;rsquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Ninja</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>This is a cooking App design inspired my mom who can always make wonders by useing foof ingredients left in the refriferator .
 Introduction This App called “FoodNinja” which offers recipes for a healthy and quick meal which can be easily processed by novices. It is also dedicated to dealing with the food ingredients left in the refrigerator in an effective way which don’t need to be worried about, just like what a Ninja can do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is the next new social media platform?</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/goisforlovers%E7%9A%84%E5%89%AF%E6%9C%AC/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/goisforlovers%E7%9A%84%E5%89%AF%E6%9C%AC/</guid>
      <description>I came up with this decentralised social network when discussing the current application of blockchain in China with my fellows in the Infinite Studio.
 The best feature of my proposed project is the equal relationship between the platform and users. Firstly, users will be able to decide the extent to which they can safely exchange their data for profits. The blockchain technology will also enable users to easily transfer their social media accounts to a safer platform without worrying about the potentially huge opportunity cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zootopia</title>
      <link>https://yining-xu.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yining-xu.com/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>A magazine design inspired by my travelling in Vietnam. *Designed it in the eternal summer of Vietnam.*`
This is my first Adobe Indesign practice: a magazine design which is inspired by my trip in the zoo at Vietnam during reading week.
Target Children are always curious about animals and treat them as friends. This magazine design aims at attracting children with cute animal silhouttes and rich colors. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>